Our sentence is 'if (both parrots talk
and quail talk) then robins talk.
I'm going to begin by replacing
the simple sentences with the
corresponding sentence letters
from the scheme of abbreviation.
I'm also going to delete that final period,
so that doesn't end up there,
and I don't notice it at the very end.
Now I need to replace
the logical connectives in English with
the corresponding connectives in
sentential logic.
I'm going to start from the inside and
work my way out.
Or as the reading sometimes puts
it
I'm going to start with the least main
connective,
which is 'both...and...', and then work my way
out to the main connective, which is
'if...then...'.
The 'Both P and Q': that is
a conjunction of P and Q.
I'm going to delete the 'both',
and I'm going to replace the 'and'
with the conjunction symbol.
And the way to enter the conjunction
symbol
with your keyboard is by typing a forward
slash,
followed by a backslash.
Carnap will redraw that,
to look nice for you.
And now I am going to replace 'if...
then...' with the arrow:
that's a minus sign, '-',
followed by the greater than sign, '>'.
There are other shortcut keys
that Carnap will recognize.
The caret symbol, '^', which you can get
by typing shift-6 on your keyboard:
it will recognize that has a conjunction.
but it won't draw it as pretty,
and it's actually no easier
to type that than it is to
type the forward slash followed by the
backlash.
Now I'm going to hit 'enter' to verify
that I have the right answer.
Actually, before I do that
let me put that period back.
Suppose I had forgotten
(to delete it) and had left the period there.
I hit enter, and it says:
"Sorry try again. That formula isn't
grammatical." That error
means that Carnap doesn't understand the
syntax of my sentence,
and that's because there's this extra period.
If my answer was just wrong,
I would get a different
error message.
Just to give you an example,
suppose that I had
snuck a negation in there, and I had
'(P ∧ Q) → ¬R',
and then I hit 'enter'.
Carnap says "Not quite! Try again.
So if the error message says
"that sentence is not grammatical",
that means that you either have a symbol
that isn't part of our vocabulary,
like a stray period.
Or it means that you might have an extra
parentheses or missing parentheses.
Or you have done something else,
that Carnap cannot parse as a
sentence.
If it can parse the sentence,
but your answer is wrong,
Carnap will say what it just said:
"Not quite! Try again."
Now I hit "enter", and it says "Perfect match!"
cuz that's the right answer.
if I was doing this as an actual
assignment, I would
click "submit", in order to be sure to get
credit for the problem.