I'm sentence is if
it pours it rains
So I will start by replacing it
pours with the sentence letter P and
it rains with the sentence letter r
I have f p e r
If Mark's p is the antecedent
Are isn't marked by anything that's
because in this
sentence there could be a helper word
then
marking the are as a consequent but
whoever
wrote this being lazy decided to delete
or
omit the helper word and just say if
it pours it rains assuming that you are
the reader would be able to figure out
that the part that is not marked it
rains must be the consequent so I'm
canonical
English this would be if P then our
And so now my job is just
to replace the English connective if men
with the logical connective of the
arrow and that is the answer