Let me show you how to complete
your first translation exercise in
Carnap.
What we have here is a sentence that we
need
to translate, that's the sentence in
English, and then it's
been repeated again in this box, where we
can edit.
And the sentence is
'If parrots talk than quail talk'.
'If' is an antecedent marker:
it marks the sentence 'parrots talk'
as the antecedent of this conditional.
'Then' is a consequent marker,
marking 'quail talk' as the consequent.
I'm going to do this step-by-step.
First, I replace the simple sentences with
their sentence letters,
following the scheme of abbreviation.
One thing I'm going
to do right now is I'm going to
delete that period.
If I have that extra period, when
I'm done that will be a stray symbol that
Carnap
doesn't understand, and it'll say that
things are wrong.
So make sure if there's a period at the end
of the English sentence to delete that.
I need to replace 'if P then Q'
with the corresponding symbol in
sentential logic.
And I want the 'if' part, which is P,
to come before the arrow,
and I want the 'then' part,
which is Q, to come after the arrow.
To type in the arrow, since I don't have an
arrow that I can type in on my keyboard,
I type hit the minus sign, '-',
followed by the greater than sign, '>'.
Carnap automatically
rewrites that to look like
a pretty arrow, not just like a minus
sign
cobbled together with a greater than sign.
I'm now done.
If I click submit right now though,
it is going to complain.
First Carnap wants me to check
whether my answer is correct.
I do that by hitting 'enter'
or 'return'.
When I hit 'enter' (or 'return'),
it says:
"Perfect match!" I then click 'OK', and now
the problem turns green with the nice
check mark,
to show me that I've correctly answered
the problem.
I still then have to also click submit
in order to get credit for the problem.
Make sure that you
are submitting your work!
When you do that you'll notice
that the number of the problem turns
green,
and that your progress bar grows at the top of
the page.