Our sentence is neither do you want
to dance nor can you dance
This is a neither nor that
you wanted to dance is q
And you can dance is
are so the sentences the
same neither Q nor are
There are two ways that are equally
good to symbolize the neither nor
statement
one way of symbolizing it captures the
idea that if neither Q nor are
that means both of those claims
are not true to say that
both of those claims are not
true is to say both not
q and not hard that is
Not Q
Are joined together
Conjunction
That is a correct answer
The other way to
symbolize neither he nor
you neither Q
Nor are
Is it follows the idea that if neither
one is true that means that it's
not the case that either one is
Then we're sayingNot.
Either one not
or are
I am so in that case we have a negation
out front
Of a disjunction and
that is also correct
You might notice that sometimes carnap
will say that one of
the answers is correct and other times
it'll say that it's
a perfect match when I create these
problems and carnap it
asked me what answer I think is the
right answer and
it says perfect match when the answer
that you give is
exactly the one that I typed it and it
says correct
when the answer that you give is
logically equivalent to the
one that I typed in in this case both of
these
answers are equally good it just happens
to be that this
is the one that I typed into the answer
key