A sentence is a long one this time it's
not the
case that if your friends don't dance
you can't dance
Now make this a little bit easier to
track
I'm going to just replace the it is
not the case that with our negation sign
But we have not if your friends don't
dance
you can't dance no really important
thing to
understand is that when you have a
phrase
like it is not the case that if
The negation cannot leap over
the F in order to
do things inside the conditional
Negation is stuck outside the
conditional
the overall form we have here
is it's not the case that
This conditional is true. Let's look at
that
conditional so your friends don't dance
that is
not pee and you can't dance that
is not far so what we have
is a conditional and the antecedent is
not pee your friends don't dance and
the consequent then is not our you
can't stand so we will delete the
English and replace it with the arrow
So that is what that symbolic sentence
means
it is the negation of the claim
that if not me then not are
so the way we say that out
loud is it is not the case
that if not P then not r