Our sentence is you can't dance and
it is not safe to dance
So I'm going to replace you can't dance
with the negation of you can dance so
you can dance is our and so you
can't dance is not our since we don't
have the negation symbol on our keyboard
we
will use the tilde to type in a
negation until December is usually above
your tab
key on the left hand side of your
keyboard and just underneath your Escape
key
You can't dance and it is not safe to
dance
that is the negation of it is safe to
dance which is s so that is not s
And finally the
conjunction and is
best and Junction
You can't dance and it is
not safe to dance is translated
into not are and not s